Guide to the George W. Wilbur Family Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- George W. Wilbur's Professional Papers, 1855-1931; Series II; 20.4; (50 boxes)
  - CASES: STREET IMPROVEMENT FILES
    - Paving in Chicago
      - "H-L" general, 1899-1901 (Box 53, Folder 1002)
        Honore Street Illinois Street Jefferson Street Keeney Avenue, and others Leavitt Street Lexington Street
      - Halsted Street, 1900-02 (Box 53, Folder 1003-1004)
        Includes both North and South Halsted Streets
      - Hamlin Avenue, 1900-07 (Box 53, Folder 1005-1008)
        Includes cases Walter H. Stone, et al. vs. The City of Chicago; and Charles P. Treat vs. William H. Johnson, et al.
      - Harrison Street, 1901-03 (Box 53, Folder 1009)
      - Harvard Avenue, 1898-1902 (Box 53, Folder 1010)
      - Irving Park Boulevard, 1899-1908 (Box 54, Folder 1011-1020)
        Includes West Irving Park Boulevard and cases The People, ex rel., John H. Thompson, County Treasurer vs. Nathan Judson, et al.; William E. Hatterman, et al. vs. The City of Chicago.
        See also: Irving Park Boulevard under Sewers, water mains in Chicago, Box 60, folder 1126
      - Kedzie Avenue, 1906 (Box 54, Folder 1021)
      - Lafayette Parkway, 1901 (Box 54, Folder 1022)
        See also: Lafayette Parkway under Sewers, water mains in Chicago, Box 55, folder 1127
      - Laflin Street, 1903-24 (Box 54, Folder 1023)
      - Lake Street, 1901-05 (Box 54, Folder 1024-1031)
        Includes West Lake Street
      - Loomis Street, 1922-23 (Box 55, Folder 1032)
        See also: Loomis Street under Sewers, water mains in Chicago, Box 60, folder 1130
      - "M-S" general, 1901 (Box 55, Folder 1033)
        West Madison Street South May Street Normal Avenue Peoria Street Sedgwick Street
      - Maxwell Street, 1901 (Box 55, Folder 1034)
      - Michigan Avenue, 1916-18 (Box 55, Folder 1035)
      - Millard Avenue, 1898, 1905 (Box 55, Folder 1036)
      - Monroe Street, 1900-01 (Box 55, Folder 1037)
        Includes West Monroe Street
      - Montrose Avenue, 1901 (Box 55, Folder 1038)
      - Ogden Avenue, 1896-1906 (Box 55, Folder 1039-1048)
        Includes case of Hannah E. Chamberlain vs. Hiram Coombs, et al.
      - Park Avenue, 1901-20 (Box 56, Folder 1049)
        Includes South Park Avenue
      - Paulina Street, 1900-20 (Box 56, Folder 1050)
        Includes both North and South Paulina Streets. Includes case City of Chicago vs. Illinois Malleable Iron Company
      - Pearce Street, 1901-03 (Box 56, Folder 1051-1052)
        Includes case W. L. De Wolf and Co. vs. The People ex rel.
      - West Randolph Street, 1920-21 (Box 56, Folder 1053)
        Includes case City of Chicago vs. National Biscuit Company, et al.
      - Rhodes Avenue, 1901-03 (Box 56, Folder 1054)
      - Ridgeway Avenue, 1901-03 (Box 56, Folder 1055-1057)
        Includes North Ridgeway Avenue
      - St. Lawrence Avenue, 1904-06 (Box 56, Folder 1058-1059)
      - Sebor Street, 1902 (Box 56, Folder 1060)
      - West Taylor Street, 1903 (Box 56, Folder 1061)
      - Tilden Avenue, 1901-02 (Box 56, Folder 1062)
        Includes case Elizabeth B. Keller vs. City of Chicago, et al.
      - Van Buren Street, 1900-03 (Box 57, Folder 1063-1067)
        Includes West Van Buren Street and case William A. Doyle vs. The People ex rel.
      - Vernon Avenue and others, 1896-1903 (Box 57, Folder 1068)
      - Wabash Avenue, 1899-1902 (Box 57, Folder 1069-1070)
      - Warren Avenue, 1896-99 (Box 57, Folder 1071-1079)
        Includes cases Daniel W. Mills, et al. vs. The City of Chicago; Caroline C. Holden, et al. vs. The City of Chicago; Fannie A. Boland, et al. vs. The City of Chicago
      - Wentworth Avenue, 1898-1905 (Box 57, Folder 1080)
      - Winchester Avenue, 1901-03 (Box 57, Folder 1081)
      - Wood Street, 1901 (Box 58, Folder 1082)
      - Numbered Streets general, 1899-1904, n.d. (Box 58, Folder 1083)
        16th Street 19th Street 32nd Street North 41st Avenue North 42nd Avenue West 58th Street 63rd Street 71st Street
      - 5th Avenue, 1901 (Box 58, Folder 1084)
      - West 12th Street, 1898 (Box 58, Folder 1085)
      - West 22nd Street, and others, 1905 (Box 58, Folder 1086)
      - 31st Street, 1900-03 (Box 58, Folder 1087-1088)
      - 40th Avenue and others, 1899-1903 (Box 58, Folder 1089-1092)
        Includes both North and South 40th Avenues
      - North 40th Court, 1906-08 (Box 58, Folder 1093-1096)
      - West 42nd Street, 1899 (Box 59, Folder 1097)
      - 43rd Avenue, 1901-02 (Box 59, Folder 1098)
        Includes North 43rd Avenue
      - 48th Street, 1900-01 (Box 59, Folder 1099)
      - 50th Avenue and others, 1901-02 (Box 59, Folder 1100)
      - West 56th Street, 1904 (Box 59, Folder 1101)
      - 64th Street, 1902-03 (Box 59, Folder 1102)
      - 65th Street, 1900-01 (Box 59, Folder 1103)
      - 66th Street, 1903 (Box 59, Folder 1104)
      - 67th Street, 1903 (Box 59, Folder 1105)
      - 88th Street, 1923 (Box 59, Folder 1106)
    - Paving in Oak Park
      - Adams Street, 1915 (Box 59, Folder 1107)
      - Alley in Hulbert's subdivision, 1922-30 (Box 59, Folder 1108)
      - Chicago Avenue, 1916-18 (Box 59, Folder 1109-1112)
        Case before State Public Utility Commission involving streetcar tracks on Chicago Avenue and Division Street
      - Division Street
        See: Chicago Avenue, Box 59, folders 1109-1112
      - Harlem Avenue, 1920-22 (Box 59, Folder 1113-1115)
      - Harvey Avenue, 1920 (Box 59, Folder 1116)
        See also: Harvey Avenue under Sewers, water mains in Oak Park, Box 60, folder 1140
      - Marion Street, 1906 (Box 59, Folder 1117)
        See also: Marion Street under Sewers, water mains in Oak Park, Box 61, folders 1141-1148
      - Paulina Street, 1906 (Box 59, Folder 1118)
        See also: Paulina Street under Sewers, water mains in Oak Park, Box 61, folder 1149
      - Pleasant Street, 1920 (Box 60, Folder 1119-1120)
    - Paving in Other Cities
      - City of Park Ridge: Home Avenue and others, 1929 (Box 60, Folder 1121)
      - Village of Maywood: South Maywood Drive, 1925 (Box 60, Folder 1122)
    - Sewers, Water Mains in Chicago
      - Ada Street, 1898 (Box 60, Folder 1123)
      - Alleys bounded by Washington Boulevard, Park Avenue, South Kedzie Avenue and South Homan Avenue, 1901 (Box 60, Folder 1124)
        See also: Alleys bounded by Washington Boulevard... under Paving in Chicago, Box 50, folder 950
      - Belmont Avenue, 1921-22 (Box 60, Folder 1125)
      - Irving Park Boulevard, 1912 (Box 60, Folder 1126)
        Case of City of Chicago vs. Ambrosia Y. Race et al.
        See also: Irving Park Boulevard under Paving in Chicago, Box 54, folders 1011-1020
      - Lafayette Parkway, 1901-03 (Box 60, Folder 1127)
        See also: Lafayette Parkway under Paving in Chicago, Box 55, folder 1127
      - West Lawrence Avenue, 1902-03 (Box 60, Folder 1128-1129)
      - Loomis Street, 1901-02 (Box 60, Folder 1130)
        See also: Loomis Street under Paving in Chicago, Box 55, folder 1032
      - West Monroe Street and others, 1929-30 (Box 60, Folder 1131-1132)
      - Van Buren Street, 1905 (Box 60, Folder 1133)
      - 14th Street, 1900-01 (Box 60, Folder 1134)
      - South 40th Avenue, 1900-01 (Box 60, Folder 1135)
      - North 41st Avenue, 1903 (Box 60, Folder 1136)
      - 48th Avenue, 1902-03 (Box 60, Folder 1137)
      - West 49th Street, 1900-01 (Box 60, Folder 1138)
      - 107th Street, 1923 (Box 60, Folder 1139)
    - Sewers, Water Mains in Oak Park
      - Harvey Avenue, 1919-20 (Box 60, Folder 1140)
        See also: Harvey Avenue under Paving in Oak Park, Box 60, folder 1140
      - Marion Street and others, 1924-28 (Box 61, Folder 1141-1148)
        See also: Marion Street under Paving in Oak Park, Box 59, folder 1117
      - Paulina Street, 1906 (Box 61, Folder 1149)
        See also: Paulina Street under Paving in Oak Park, Box 61, folder 1118
    - Sewers, Water Mains in West Hammond
      - Plummer Avenue, 1906 (Box 61, Folder 1150)
    - Subway in Chicago
      - State Street and other streets, 1931 (Box 61, Folder 1151)
    - Miscellaneous
      - Research notes, n.d. (Box 61, Folder 1152-1153)
      - Fragments, 1901-22 (Box 61, Folder 1154)
  - CASES: OTHER CASE FILES
    - Ahl, Alice V. vs. Clarence H. Ahl, 1921 (Box 61, Folder 1155)
    - Bell, John P. vs. Dorr E. Felt, et al. (Box 61, Folder 1156-1161)
    - Berger, Elkan vs. Linus Ewald Roder, 1930 (Box 62, Folder 1162)
    - Brown, Charles A. vs. Clarkson Glue Co., 1918-22 (Box 62, Folder 1163-1164)
    - Buell, Horace W. vs. Pearl Buell, 1920-26 (Box 62, Folder 1165)
    - Caruguss Manufacturing Co. vs. Kelling-Karel Co., 1919-21 (Box 62, Folder 1166-1169)
    - Cohen, Samuel vs. Toy Gun Manufacturing Company, 1908-12 (Box 62, Folder 1170)
    - Coleman, Lena Shaw, 1919-26 (Box 62, Folder 1171-1174)
    - Connors, Daniel vs. Peter Ambrosini, 1901-02 (Box 62, Folder 1175)
    - Dauchy, Cordelia and Delia Day, 1916 (Box 62, Folder 1176)
      Oil and gas lease in Nebraska
    - Dombroski, Peter vs. Nimick, John, et al., 1924 (Box 62, Folder 1177)
    - Eastman, Ernest A., 1899-1902 (Box 62, Folder 1178)
    - Eastman, Roger and Georgie M., 1891 (Box 62, Folder 1179)
    - Engineering Agency, Inc. vs. R. B. Fralick, 1925-27 (Box 62, Folder 1180)
    - Falk, S. vs. Louis Seybold, 1906 (Box 62, Folder 1181)
    - Farrell, Thomas F. et al vs. West Chicago Park Commissioners, 1899-1900 (Box 62, Folder 1182)
    - Fuller, Alonzo M. vs. Charles T. Luckow and The Globe Laundry Co., 1917-25 (Box 63, Folder 1183-1186)
      See also: Alonzo M. Fuller vs. Webb S. Edwards filed under contracts, Box 28, folder 610
    - Gaskill, John B. [The People ex rel.] vs. The Forest Home Cemetery Co. of Chicago, et al., 1913-14 (Box 63, Folder 1187)
      Notes on case involving an African-American's cemetery rights
    - General Acceptance Co. vs. Gustav E. Anderson, et al., 1926-28 (Box 63, Folder 1188)
    - Hall, Agnes vs. Richard F. Geraghty, 1924-25 (Box 63, Folder 1189)
    - Higgie, Mary J., 1906-27 (Box 63, Folder 1190)
    - Jones, Mary A., 1926 (Box 63, Folder 1191)
    - Joyce, John J. vs. National Surface Guard Co., 1919-21 (Box 63, Folder 1192-1194)
    - Julin, Anton C., 1922-27 (Box 63, Folder 1195)
    - Kleinedler, Fred M., 1922 (Box 63, Folder 1196)
    - Knudson, Charles B., 1921-28 (Box 63, Folder 1197-1205)
    - Lake, Frank C., 1891-1915 (Box 64, Folder 1206-1207)
    - Larsen, Mary vs. Mr. and Mrs. Charles Olander, 1921-24 (Box 64, Folder 1208-1209)
    - Loren, Otto, 1922 (Box 64, Folder 1210)
    - Martensen, Harold N., 1929-30 (Box 64, Folder 1211)
    - Massachusetts Broken Stone Co., 1924-25 (Box 64, Folder 1212)
    - Mattison, Frank S. vs. Kersey M. Woodward, et al., 1929 (Box 64, Folder 1213)
    - Melville, Americus B., 1926-27 (Box 64, Folder 1214)
      See also: Americus B. Melville vs. Charles H. Woodward under Contracts, Box 29, folders 624-631
    - Mercy Hospital, 1908-09 (Box 64, Folder 1215-1216)
    - Oak Park General Taxes, 1930 (Box 64, Folder 1217)
    - People vs. Edward O. Baker, 1903-05 (Box 64, Folder 1218)
    - People vs. The City of Oak Ridge, 1922-23 (Box 64, Folder 1219-1223)
    - People vs. Joseph D. Herbert, 1930 (Box 64, Folder 1224)
    - Pray & Sons vs. Llewellyn Jones, 1921-22 (Box 64, Folder 1225)
    - Reading, Sarah C., 1921-28 (Box 65, Folder 1226-1234)
    - Reidy, Olive E. and Thomas J., 1927 (Box 65, Folder 1235)
    - Reuter, Ernest, 1921-24 (Box 65, Folder 1236-1238)
      See also: August and Ernest Reuter in Real Estate, Box 48, folder 920
    - Robbel, Richard A., 1919-27 (Box 65, Folder 1239-1241)
    - Rockey, Charles F. vs. R. J. Walters, 1924 (Box 65, Folder 1242)
    - Saint Francis Xavier Female Academy, 1907-08 (Box 65, Folder 1243)
    - Schwartz, Josiah, 1901 (Box 65, Folder 1244)
    - Simo, Paul, 1924 (Box 65, Folder 1245)
    - Stark, Andrew, 1898-1902 (Box 65, Folder 1246)
    - Strobl, Samuel vs. John Zidek, Jr., 1922-23 (Box 65, Folder 1247)
    - Sweaney, James B., 1929-30 (Box 65, Folder 1248)
    - Thomas, L. H., 1901 (Box 65, Folder 1249)
    - Thurber, William, 1922 (Box 65, Folder 1250)
    - U. S. Rolling Stock Company, 1893 (Box 66, Folder 1251)
    - Walker, John A., 1922-24 (Box 66, Folder 1252)
    - Wheeler, G. S. vs. A. Schulenburg, 1923 (Box 66, Folder 1253)
    - Wickstrom, Helen, 1930 (Box 66, Folder 1254)
    - Wrzeszcz, Anna and Joseph, 1926 (Box 66, Folder 1255)
  - CASES: FRAGMENTS FROM FILES
    - Fragments, 1875-1909 (Box 66, Folder 1256)
    - Fragments, 1915 (Box 66, Folder 1257)
    - Fragments, 1917-31 (Box 66, Folder 1258)
    - Fragments, n.d. (Box 66, Folder 1259-1263)
  - PROFESSIONAL CORRESPONDENCE
    - Correspondence, 1874 (Box 67, Folder 1264-1265)
    - Correspondence, 1875-76 (Box 67, Folder 1266)
    - Correspondence, 1877 (Box 67, Folder 1267-1268)
    - Correspondence, 1878-83 (Box 67, Folder 1269)
    - Letterpress book, [1879]-84
      See: Oversize, Box 111, folder 1845
    - Correspondence, 1884 (Box 67, Folder 1270)
    - Correspondence, 1885 (Box 67, Folder 1271)
    - Correspondence, 1886 (Box 67, Folder 1272-1273)
    - Correspondence, 1887 (Box 67, Folder 1274-1282)
    - Correspondence, 1888 (Box 67, Folder 1283-1286)
    - Correspondence, 1889 (Box 67, Folder 1287)
    - Correspondence, 1890 (Box 67, Folder 1288-1294)
    - Correspondence, 1891 (Box 68, Folder 1295-1300)
    - Correspondence, 1893-96 (Box 68, Folder 1301)
    - Correspondence, 1897 (Box 68, Folder 1302-1309)
    - Correspondence, 1898 (Box 68, Folder 1310-1322)
    - Correspondence, 1899 Jan-Feb (Box 68, Folder 1323-1325)
    - Correspondence, 1899 Mar-Dec (Box 69, Folder 1326-1330)
    - Correspondence, 1900 (Box 69, Folder 1331-1334)
    - Correspondence, 1901 (Box 69, Folder 1335-1336)
    - Correspondence, 1902 (Box 69, Folder 1337)
    - Correspondence, 1903 (Box 69, Folder 1338-1339)
    - Correspondence, 1904 (Box 69, Folder 1340-1341)
    - Correspondence, 1905 (Box 69, Folder 1342)
    - Correspondence, 1906 (Box 69, Folder 1343)
    - Correspondence, 1907 (Box 69, Folder 1344-1345)
    - Correspondence, 1911-14 (Box 69, Folder 1346)
    - Correspondence, 1916 (Box 69, Folder 1347)
    - Correspondence, 1917-19 (Box 69, Folder 1348)
    - Correspondence, 1920 (Box 69, Folder 1349)
    - Correspondence, 1921 (Box 69, Folder 1350-1351)
    - Correspondence, 1922 (Box 69, Folder 1352)
    - Correspondence, 1923 (Box 69, Folder 1353-1354)
    - Correspondence, 1924 (Box 69, Folder 1355)
    - Correspondence, 1925 (Box 69, Folder 1356-1357)
    - Correspondence, 1926 (Box 70, Folder 1358-1360)
    - Correspondence, 1927 (Box 70, Folder 1361-1362)
    - Correspondence, 1928 (Box 70, Folder 1363-1366)
    - Correspondence, 1929 (Box 70, Folder 1367-1368)
    - Correspondence, 1930-31 (Box 70, Folder 1369)
    - Correspondence (Box 70, Folder 1370-1371)
    - Stationery pad, n.d. (Box 71, Folder 1372)
  - FINANCIAL RECORDS
    - Account books, 1895-1918 (Box 71, Folder 1373-1377)
    - Bills and receipts, 1874-90 (Box 71, Folder 1378)
    - Bills and receipts, 1891-94 (Box 71, Folder 1379)
    - Bills and receipts, 1895 (Box 71, Folder 1380)
    - Bills and receipts, 1896 (Box 71, Folder 1381)
    - Bills and receipts, 1897 (Box 71, Folder 1382)
    - Bills and receipts, 1898 (Box 71, Folder 1383)
    - Bills and receipts, 1899 (Box 71, Folder 1384)
    - Bills and receipts, 1900 (Box 71, Folder 1385)
    - Bills and receipts, 1901 (Box 72, Folder 1386)
    - Bills and receipts, 1902 (Box 72, Folder 1387)
    - Bills and receipts, 1903 (Box 72, Folder 1388)
    - Bills and receipts, 1904 (Box 72, Folder 1389)
    - Bills and receipts, 1905 (Box 72, Folder 1390-1391)
    - Bills and receipts, 1906 (Box 72, Folder 1392-1393)
    - Bills and receipts, 1907 (Box 72, Folder 1394-1395)
    - Bills and receipts, 1908 (Box 72, Folder 1396-1397)
    - Bills and receipts, 1909 (Box 72, Folder 1398)
    - Bills and receipts, 1910 (Box 72, Folder 1399)
    - Bills and receipts, 1911 (Box 72, Folder 1400)
    - Bills and receipts, 1912 (Box 72, Folder 1401)
    - Bills and receipts, 1913 (Box 72, Folder 1402)
    - Bills and receipts, 1914 (Box 72, Folder 1403)
    - Bills and receipts, 1915 (Box 72, Folder 1404)
    - Bills and receipts, 1916 (Box 72, Folder 1405)
    - Bills and receipts, 1917 (Box 72, Folder 1406)
    - Bills and receipts, 1918 (Box 72, Folder 1407)
    - Bills and receipts, 1919 (Box 72, Folder 1408)
    - Bills and receipts, 1920 (Box 72, Folder 1409)
    - Bills and receipts, 1921 (Box 73, Folder 1410)
    - Bills and receipts, 1922 (Box 73, Folder 1411)
    - Bills and receipts, 1923 (Box 73, Folder 1412)
    - Bills and receipts, 1924 (Box 73, Folder 1413)
    - Bills and receipts, 1925 (Box 73, Folder 1414)
    - Bills and receipts, 1926 (Box 73, Folder 1415)
    - Bills and receipts, 1927 (Box 73, Folder 1416)
    - Bills and receipts (Box 73, Folder 1417)
    - Day Book, 1895-1900 (Box 73, Folder 1418)
    - Expense Notebooks and Journals
      - Business trip to Maine and Massachusetts, 1883 (Box 73, Folder 1419)
        Trip made to negotiate settlement in divorce of Albert H. and Carrie Gale.
        See also: Series I, folders 375-377, 495-503
      - Business trips to Kingman, Kansas and Fond du Lac, Wisconsin, 1890 (Box 73, Folder 1420)
      - Business trip to Washington, D.C., 1900 Oct (Box 73, Folder 1421)
      - Business trips to Ohio, New York, Colorado, Kansas, Kentucky, and within Illinois, 1902-18 (Box 73, Folder 1422)
      - Business trip to Summerdale, Alabama, 1916 (Box 73, Folder 1423)
      - Business trip to San Francisco; Springfield and Rock Island, Illinois, 1920 (Box 73, Folder 1424)
        Trip to San Francisco made for Robert L. Burke.
        See also: Series II, Cases: Long Term Individual Client Files of Michael and Robert L. Burke, folders 657-702
    - Matthews, Webb P. statements, 1901-02 (Box 73, Folder 1425)
      Dispute over wages paid to him as George Wilbur's office boy
  - NOTEBOOKS
    - Attorney's office docket, 1881-96 (Box 74, Folder 1426-1427)
    - Case directory, 1890-92 (Box 74, Folder 1428)
    - Case directory, c. 1893 (Box 74, Folder 1429)
    - Case directories, n.d. (Box 74, Folder 1430-1431)
    - Justice docket, 1891-1906 (Box 75, Folder 1432)
    - Pocket notebook (Box 75, Folder 1433)
      - Docket information for mostly Ruby Chief Mining Company cases in front, mining notes in back, c. 1888
  - PRINTED MATERIAL
    - An Act Concerning Local Improvements, 1922 (Box 75, Folder 1434)
    - Chicago Bar Association
      - Record, vol. 7, nos. 8, 9, 1924 May-Jun (Box 75, Folder 1434a)
      - Report of Committee on Permanent Home, 1923 (Box 75, Folder 1434b)
      - Report of the President of the Chicago Bar Association for the Year 1922-23, and 1923-24 (Box 75, Folder 1434c)
    - Counsellor's Chorus, 1909 (Box 75, Folder 1435)
    - Diaries for the Bar of Cook County, 1901-02 (Box 75, Folder 1436)
    - Diaries for the Bar of Cook County, 1902-03 (Box 75, Folder 1437)
    - Docket Supreme Court of Illinois
      - Bound volumes, 1897-1920 (Box 76, Folder 1438)
      - Individual pamphlets, 1920-22 (Box 77, Folder 1439)
      - Individual pamphlets, 1923-26 (Box 77, Folder 1440)
    - Illinois State Bar Association program, 1915 (Box 77, Folder 1440a)
    - Invitation to Illinois State Bar Association Banquet, 1923 Nov 30 (Box 77, Folder 1441)
- George W. Wilbur's Personal and Business Papers, 1867-1931; Series III; 6.7; (17 boxes)
  Series III, George W. Wilbur's Personal and Business Papers, is organized into five subseries: Diaries, Personal Financial Records, Business Records, Writings, and Other Papers.
  - DIARIES
    - Diaries, 1874-79 (Box 78, Folder 1442-1447)
    - Paper cutout found in George W. Wilbur's 1879 diary (Box 78, Folder 1448)
    - Diaries, 1880-85 (Box 79, Folder 1449-1454)
    - Diaries, 1886-90 (Box 80, Folder 1455-1459)
    - Diaries, 1891-95 (Box 81, Folder 1460-1464)
    - Diaries, 1896-1930 (Box 82, Folder 1465-1469)
    - Diary, 1930-[31] (Box 83, Folder 1470)
  - PERSONAL FINANCIAL RECORDS
    - Account Books
      - Account book, 1865-74
        See: Series IV, Account book of Sarah Ann Cook Wilbur, folders 1681-1682
      - House expenses, 1900-06 (Box 83, Folder 1471)
    - Bills and Receipts
      - Bills and receipts, 1872-89 (Box 83, Folder 1472)
      - Bills and receipts, 1890-92 (Box 83, Folder 1472a)
      - A-C (Box 84, Folder 1473-1476)
      - Cicero Water, Gas & Electric Company, 1894-99 (Box 84, Folder 1477)
      - D-J (Box 84, Folder 1478-1481)
      - K-R (Box 84, Folder 1482-1485)
      - S-Z (Box 85, Folder 1486-1488)
      - A-G (Box 85, Folder 1489-1490)
      - E. J. Gotsch Grocery and Market, 1901-05 (Box 85, Folder 1491)
      - H-P (Box 85, Folder 1492-1493)
      - Marshall Field & Company, 1901-05 (Box 85, Folder 1494)
      - W. H. Whittlesey & Company, 1901-05 (Box 85, Folder 1495)
      - S-Z (Box 85, Folder 1496-1498)
      - A-F (Box 85, Folder 1499-1500)
      - E. J. Gotsch Company Grocery and Market, 1906-07 (Box 85, Folder 1501)
      - H-R (Box 86, Folder 1502-1503)
      - Marshall Field & Company, 1906-07 (Box 86, Folder 1504)
      - S-Z (Box 86, Folder 1505-1506)
      - A-F (Box 86, Folder 1507-1508)
      - E. J. Gotsch Company Grocery and Market, 1908-11 (Box 86, Folder 1509)
      - G-M (Box 86, Folder 1510-1512)
      - Marshall Field & Company, 1908-11 (Box 86, Folder 1513-1514)
      - N-S (Box 87, Folder 1515-1517)
      - T-Z (Box 87, Folder 1518-1519)
      - A-E (Box 87, Folder 1520-1521)
      - Belz Brothers, 1912-26 (Box 87, Folder 1522)
      - E. J. Gotsch Company, 1912-26 (Box 87, Folder 1523-1524)
      - G-L (Box 87, Folder 1525)
      - M-S (Box 87, Folder 1526-1529)
      - Marshall Field & Company, 1912-26 (Box 88, Folder 1530-1531)
      - Quick Service Taxi Company, 1912-26 (Box 88, Folder 1532)
      - T-Z (Box 88, Folder 1533-1535)
      - Bills and receipts (Box 88, Folder 1536)
    - Checks (canceled) and Check Registers
      - Check register, 1889-91 (Box 88, Folder 1537)
      - Checks (canceled) and check registers, 1893-99 (Box 88, Folder 1538)
        See: Restricted Fragile Papers, Box 116
      - Check register, 1909-12 (Box 88, Folder 1539)
      - Check register, 1912-13 (Box 88, Folder 1540)
      - Checks (canceled) and check registers, 1913-19 (Box 89, Folder 1541-1546)
      - Checks (canceled) and check registers, 1919-22 (Box 90, Folder 1547-1549)
    - Housekeeping Correspondence
      - With Irving Terwilliger (banker)
        - Correspondence, 1872-74 (Box 91, Folder 1550)
        - Correspondence, 1875 (Box 91, Folder 1551-1552)
        - Correspondence, 1876 (Box 91, Folder 1553-1554)
        - Correspondence, 1877 (Box 91, Folder 1555)
        - Correspondence, 1878 (Box 91, Folder 1556-1557)
        - Correspondence, 1879-86 (Box 91, Folder 1558)
        - Correspondence, 1887-98 (Box 91, Folder 1559)
      - With Others
        - Correspondence, 1873-78 (Box 91, Folder 1560)
        - Correspondence, 1882-87 (Box 91, Folder 1561)
        - Correspondence, 1888-90 (Box 91, Folder 1562)
        - Correspondence, 1891-98 (Box 91, Folder 1563)
        - Correspondence, 1899-1901 (Box 91, Folder 1564)
        - Correspondence, 1904-06 (Box 91, Folder 1565)
        - Correspondence, 1912-20 (Box 91, Folder 1566)
        - Correspondence, 1925-31 (Box 91, Folder 1567)
        - Correspondence (Box 91, Folder 1568)
  - BUSINESS RECORDS
    - McLaughlin Smoke Consumer Company
      - Bills and receipts, 1884-88 (Box 92, Folder 1569)
      - Contracts, 1884-86 (Box 92, Folder 1570-1571)
      - Correspondence, 1884-96 (Box 92, Folder 1572-1573)
        See also: Correspondence for 1884 in Letterpress Book, Box 111, folder 1845
    - Milling and Mining
      - Bills and receipts, 1890 (Box 92, Folder 1574)
      - Bills and receipts, 1891 (Box 92, Folder 1575-1578)